[{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664727478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":7199,"timeElapsed":55651},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664732286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":4799,"timeElapsed":60459},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664739729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":7439,"timeElapsed":67903},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664754552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":14821,"timeElapsed":82726},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664759689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5133,"timeElapsed":87862},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664764358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4666,"timeElapsed":92532},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664774016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":9654,"timeElapsed":102189},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664778786,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4768,"timeElapsed":106960},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664783618,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4830,"timeElapsed":111792},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665006934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":222323,"timeElapsed":335108},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665010510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3573,"timeElapsed":338684},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665013566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":3053,"timeElapsed":341740},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665016593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3019,"timeElapsed":344767},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665018714,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2120,"timeElapsed":346888},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665021564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2847,"timeElapsed":349737},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665025829,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4257,"timeElapsed":354003},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665028221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2388,"timeElapsed":356394},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665030427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2202,"timeElapsed":358601},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665193986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":162643,"timeElapsed":522159},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665196096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2099,"timeElapsed":524270},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665200336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4235,"timeElapsed":528510},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665203197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2857,"timeElapsed":531371},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665207112,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3908,"timeElapsed":535286},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665235115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":27994,"timeElapsed":563288},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665238562,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3441,"timeElapsed":566735},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665240399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1830,"timeElapsed":568573},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665241517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1117,"timeElapsed":569691},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665244408,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2889,"timeElapsed":572582},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665253031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":7761,"timeElapsed":581205},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665255504,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2469,"timeElapsed":583678},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665259109,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3601,"timeElapsed":587282},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665262157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3041,"timeElapsed":590331},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665265969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3806,"timeElapsed":594143},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665268221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2250,"timeElapsed":596395},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665271259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3035,"timeElapsed":599433},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665273325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2061,"timeElapsed":601498},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665274569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1241,"timeElapsed":602743},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665275907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1336,"timeElapsed":604081},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665280765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3993,"timeElapsed":608939},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665282516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1750,"timeElapsed":610690},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665284922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2405,"timeElapsed":613096},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665287956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":3032,"timeElapsed":616130},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665290162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2204,"timeElapsed":618336},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665291895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":1730,"timeElapsed":620068},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665293664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1766,"timeElapsed":621838},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665295913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2247,"timeElapsed":624086},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665298619,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2702,"timeElapsed":626793},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665326382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":26775,"timeElapsed":654556},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665334691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":8306,"timeElapsed":662865},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665337150,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":2457,"timeElapsed":665324},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665338748,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":1597,"timeElapsed":666922},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665340618,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":1868,"timeElapsed":668792},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665343581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2962,"timeElapsed":671755},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665345101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1518,"timeElapsed":673275},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665346615,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1512,"timeElapsed":674789},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665347985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1368,"timeElapsed":676159},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665465089,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":111176,"timeElapsed":793263},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665467087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1996,"timeElapsed":795261},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665468694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":1603,"timeElapsed":796868},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665479944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":11248,"timeElapsed":808118},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665487193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":7245,"timeElapsed":815367},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665495084,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7882,"timeElapsed":823258},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665498111,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3024,"timeElapsed":826285},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665500778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2664,"timeElapsed":828952},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665502592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1809,"timeElapsed":830766},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665516175,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":12595,"timeElapsed":844349},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665518557,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2380,"timeElapsed":846731},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665520723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2163,"timeElapsed":848897},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665524065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3341,"timeElapsed":852239},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665526214,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2148,"timeElapsed":854388},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665528473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2255,"timeElapsed":856646},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665531146,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2665,"timeElapsed":859320},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665535508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":4357,"timeElapsed":863682},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665537072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1559,"timeElapsed":865246},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665548504,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":10214,"timeElapsed":876678},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665551437,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2932,"timeElapsed":879611},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665554096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2657,"timeElapsed":882270},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665556134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2035,"timeElapsed":884307},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665557511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":1372,"timeElapsed":885684},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665558843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1331,"timeElapsed":887017},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665561999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3153,"timeElapsed":890173},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665564494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2492,"timeElapsed":892668},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665567348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":2853,"timeElapsed":895522},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665574000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5646,"timeElapsed":902174},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665577301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3297,"timeElapsed":905475},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665579189,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1884,"timeElapsed":907363},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665583962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4770,"timeElapsed":912136},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665590717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6754,"timeElapsed":918891},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665592964,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2242,"timeElapsed":921138},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665594448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":1481,"timeElapsed":922622},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665602226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":7774,"timeElapsed":930399},{"subjectID":"px7xflq8oo","prolificID":"670a165e0ef22b0779d470dd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215a25291c7949368a6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665606347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4116,"timeElapsed":934519}]